

JINAL MATHURA BHANUSHALI

Reach me at:

D-402, Shiv Parvati Complex, N.S.S. Road, Himalaya Society (Asalpha), Ghatkopar (w), Mumbai- 400084 Contact no.- 7045327545 Jinalb333@gmail.com D.O.B.- 9th May, 1996

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

A self-motivated, highly passionate, result oriented, young energetic professional with focused experience in Sales & Marketing, Market research and Business Development (online & offline businesses). Putting together the teams and leading the initiative independently. Capability to build customer relation and provide benefits to the organisation by serving the best to them.

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office(Excel, PowerPoint, Word)
- Well educated to handle digitized technologies & strategies.
- Social media handling /marketing
- Content management
- Knowledge oriented to digital advertisements
- Expertized in Sales growth, target achievement with customer satisfaction
- Knowledge of handling and resolving customer queries.
- Experience in dealing with B2B & B2C
- Market research strategies.
- Marketing Strategies related to gather public opinions and interests

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales, Branding, Market Research in Educational Field, Branding Agency for Pharmaceuticals and Gaming sector.

Senior Business Development - 15th June 2017 - 13th March 2018 uFaber Edutech Pvt Ltd. — Mumbai

Worked as a Senior Business Development Executive.

Worked on the Online Education platform. Define and implement new strategies that align with client's business requirement.

Implementation of new ideas to Digitize Education in India Counselling aspirants for their examination.

To use my sales and marketing oriented skills in the best possible way for achieving the company's sales goals.

Define and implement new strategies that align with business profit

Come up with ideas that will help generate more business

Aimed at generating more business for the company by identifying the needs and wants of the customer and providing the product accordingly.

To not only sell the product but look after the satisfactory point of the customer.

To create sales business strategies and develop existing customer sales, marketing tools and product launching.

Business Development Associate - 21st March 2018 - 31st May 2018 Brandbucks

Worked on an offline platform, to showcase the branding inputs to clients (PMT's) of pharmaceutical companies and build relations and bring business for the company by analysing the client's product needs and arranging ideas accordingly.

Rapport Building with clients.

Lead generation.

Product requirements, alterations fulfilment.

 ${\bf Engaging\ with\ Product\ Managers.}$

Effective communication skills.

Good Presentation Skills.

Business Development Collaborator -27th December 2018 - 6th March 2019 VNG (Vietnam Gaming Company)

Worked on **contract base of 2 months**, to study the market opportunity for the company to enter in India in gaming sector. Where role was to do market research for Mumbai city and provide with the calculated results to the firm with all honesty and dedication. Role also included:

Game testing and review.

Social media handlina.

Fan page management on Facebook.

Ways, methods and ideas of gathering reviews both online as well as offline. Sorting out the target area and people for marketing and engaging in the game. Business Development Executive (Sales) - 11th April 2019 - 10th September 2019- Almats Branding Solutions Pvt. Ltd.(Printing Company)

Worked for the company in field sales. Where meeting the marketing managers of various high- ended companies and cracking the deal for profits was the major goal. Here completing the targets was not the only obstacle but engaging with clients & building relation & bond with them was one.

Meeting Procurement managers & Marketing managers, knowing & fulfilling their needs for printing with creative ideas, following up with various teams like inhouse sales, paper procurement, factory, printing press, dummy makers etc & making it happen by closing the deal with highest requirements & sales was the only motive for me.

Managing clients
Building Rapport
Closing deals
Finding Prospects
Creating Relationship/ Bond
Managing Report\

Sales Review

EDUCATION

- PURSUING HYBRID PGDM FROM WELINGKAR (2017-2019)
- GRADUATED IN BACHELOR OF MANAGEMENT STUDIES -B.M.S. (2014 - 2017)
- MSG- SGKM UNIVERSAL COLLEGE OF ARTS, SCIENCE & COMMERCE

(MUMBAI UNIVERSITY).

- CLASS OBTAINED : 2ND
- STATE: MAHARASHTRA
- S.S.C. (2012)
- H.S.C.(2014)
- -D.J. DOSHI GURUKUL COLLEGE OF COMMERCE
- -CLASS OBTAINED : 1ST
- -STATE :MAHARASHTRA
- -R.N. GANDHI HIGH SCHOOL MSBSHE
- -CLASS OBTAINED: 1ST
- -STATE :MAHARASHTRA

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION / COURSES

- CERTIFIED DIGITAL MARKETING COURSE -SOCIALOPEDIA (DETAILED) - 2018
- E.C.E. COURSE (EARLY CHILDHOOD EDUCATION)
- TALLY
- MS-CIT
- DIPLOMA IN SOFTWARE PROGRAMMING

INTERESTS

- SKETCHING
- DOODLE
- MUSIC
- RIDING

